http://www.vitaman.com.au/pages/terms-conditions

19th Dec - Express Post
This privacy policy governs the manner in which VITAMAN GLOBAL collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information from users ("User") via the vitamanglobal.co website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site as well as to all products and services offered by VITAMAN GLOBAL.
Personal Identification Information
We may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to: when Users visit the Site, register as a VITAMAN GLOBAL preferred customer, and in connection with other activities, services, features, and resources on our Site. Users may also be asked to provide their email address for identification purposes, to complete a purchase, or to receive promotional communications, as appropriate.
We will only collect personal information from Users if they voluntarily provide it to us. Users can choose what information they provide to us, fully knowing that refusing to provide certain kinds of personal information may prevent them from engaging in various Site-related activities or transactions.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. This information may include: browser name, type of computer used to access the Site, and other technical information related operating systems, Internet service providers, and other similar information.
Web Browser Cookies
Websites place cookies on hard drives (computer, mobile device, etc.) to store information about a User’s visit to that site, including: preferred language and currency, location, and other personal settings. Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance and customise the User experience in a variety of ways. Users may choose to disable cookies (i.e. not give websites permission to leave cookies on their hard drive) or set up alerts that notify them whenever a website uses cookies. By choosing to disable cookies, please note that some of the Site features and functionality may not work properly.
How We Use Collected Information
VITAMAN GLOBAL collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To Improve Customer Service
Your information helps us more effectively respond to customer support requests or address specific customer needs. It also helps us better communicate with Users about shipping delays, out-of-stock products, and other matters related to order processing.
To Send Periodic Emails
The email address Users provide for order processing will only be used to send information and updates pertaining to orders. It may also be used to respond to other User-initiated inquiries, requests, and questions. If a User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they should expect to receive emails about company news, product updates, seasonal promotions, and other product- or service-related information. Users may opt-out of email communications at any time via the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of our emails or by contacting us directly via our Site.
How We Protect Your Information
We follow the appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and implement relevant security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of personal information, including usernames, passwords, transaction information, payment details, and other User-related data stored on our Site.
All sensitive and private data exchanged between the Site and its Users takes place over an encrypted SSL (“Secure Socet Layer”) secured communications channel for added protection.
Sharing Your Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, or provide access to our Users’ personal information to third party sources. We may share generic, aggregated demographic information, not linked to any personal information whatsoever, regarding our Users and their behaviors on our Site with business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers. We may use third party service providers to help operate parts of our business, including our Site, or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out emails, surveys, contests, etc. In these rare instances only, we may ask to share personal information to enhance the User experience and will only do so once Users have provided permission.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
VITAMAN GLOBAL has the discretion to update its privacy policy at any time. All changes to our privacy policy will be communicated to Users and posted prominently on our Site. We encourage Users to visit this page frequently to stay informed about how we use and protect the personal information provided to us. It is the User’s responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically.
Accepting These Terms
By using this Site, you accept our privacy policy and terms of service. Similarly, continued use of the Site following any changes to the privacy policy shall be deemed acceptance of those changes. If you do not agree with our privacy policy in any way or have any issues with the aforementioned statements within this policy, it is at your sole discretion to no longer visit the Site.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the information on this Site, or your transactions with this Site, please do not hesitate to contact us at:
VITAMAN GLOBALPO BOX 622 Fairfield NSW 1860
Send us an email
"Close (esc)"
x
Powered By Discount Ninja
×
[[BODY]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1_LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2_LABEL]]
×
[[HEADER]]
[[MINIMIZED]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[TEXT]]
×
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[TEXT]]
[[HEADER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[BODY]]
[[QUANTITY_LABEL]]
[[PRICE_LABEL]]
[[TIER_ROW]]
[[PRICE]]
[[LABEL]]
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ROW]]
